question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Bill Cipher in the show &quot;Gravity Falls&quot; is the good guy.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Waylon Smithers from &quot;The Simpsons&quot; was originally black when he first "
                 "appeared in the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disney&#039;s 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film "
                 "Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Blue Danube was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Snagglepuss was part of the Yogi Yahooies in the 1977 show Scooby&#039;s All-Star Laff-a-Lympics.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, Lavabending is "
                 "a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
